[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard love
podcast
at what age do we learn how to have
better conversations
at what age do we learn to have better
conversations with ourselves
[Music]
my
knowledge is power
hello welcome to the junkyard love
podcast
it is me your host dobby the house elf
today we have my friend shiloh reister
on the podcast
this episode has a particular beauty
about it because
shiloh's dog has actually since passed
away
she texted me a couple days after the
episode and told me the news
and i asked her if she wanted to you
know re-record the episode
her dog was in her lap a lot of the
times i wasn't sure how that would be
difficult for her but she said
you know we talked about the world
needing more dogs right now
there's a few synchronicities we're
talking about our k-line canine
connections with humans and dogs
throughout the episode
and she said i think we should certainly
keep it i think we should certainly put
it out
um and i agree so uh
it has that that extra beauty in it you
know listening back after learning this
information
it just seemed a lot more a lot more
genuine a lot more real
um and i also i also something i tend to
do with the podcast is i don't
i try not to edit too much actually i
try to keep it this authentic
for me i feel when you could hear people
messing up or stumbling over their words
or you can hear you know someone walks
in front of the camera you know as long
as it doesn't
take you away too much there's even a
slight delay throughout the episode with
this
it takes us a few minutes to kind of get
the bearings rolling but
to me there's there's impressiveness in
humans ability to
um get through all this and still
connect you know to still have like
interruptions or still have
um you know a dog in our lap and be able
to have a serious conversation
so i didn't edit it much i kept it kind
of as is and i think that you'll see
and experience and hear why um
but yeah so this episode has a
particular beauty about it um
shiloh has has lost her her companion
her friend georgia peach so
if you are her friend you know maybe
maybe reach out and give her your
condolences
we could all use each other right now
maybe just a quick text quick little
reach out to
people who are going through loss right
now just like all of us so
without further ado let's get going with
the episode
it is me georgia peach and shiloh
reister i hope you enjoy
i got my puppy georgia right
yeah yeah
it's a little dim in here but
yeah she's big
she thinks she thinks she's a lap dog
even though she's clearly what
but yeah i have um
my dog blue is not here he's uh
shaylee and i are like sharing custody
with him so it's always just back and
forth
um but i think that we have like kennel
cough
breaking out in the house because my
roommates they have two dogs and one of
them has kennel cough and
one of our friends in portland had it um
their dog so we're
trying to deal with that like trying to
not give all the dogs kennel cough if we
can help it but
yeah poor little buds how does that even
happen
like i i don't know i mean i know it's
pretty prevalent in pounds um
and like like humane society i feel like
they they get it fairly often
i'm not sure if it's like a dog cold or
if it's more severe like doggy covid or
something but
i know that um the the scary part of it
is that it could lead to pneumonia so
like older dogs it's
it's a little more scary for them i
guess but i also really don't know that
much i just
quick google search is all i get so
yeah no i was always
curious of how it you know
how it happens and everything like that
because i've never had to deal with it
but
with our dogs yeah i think um i think
you can get antibiotics for it like
for the dog but i'm not sure again i
don't know enough about it to know if
that's like
safe thing or if they always need
antibiotics or if because dogs are
pretty
like resilient they'll just their immune
systems will just power through or
whatever they're sick for a couple days
and then
they're good but okay um
i i am recording my friend
let me see video
oh man as soon as i say i'm recording
then it minimizes me
there we go shiloh what do you like to
go
go by what's what's the last name middle
name you like to go by
reister yeah okay yeah because i don't
know you know sometimes we have our
um on social media we'll change our like
into our middle name or it'll be
something else so i'm always clarifying
because sometimes you just think
everybody goes by the same name all the
time but
i usually like first name shy but
shy shiloh yeah
okay usually hello shiloh
welcome to the junkyard love podcast
hello it's nice to have you on here
um we had been trying to make it work
for a while because we were living close
closer quarters actually at the old
house but then you started getting
scheduled right as i was
beginning to um move
and get out of that old studio so it's
cool that we're able to still connect
via zoom it's not the same but
it's still still something
yeah it's always nice
what has your life you've
you've been experiencing the old covid
quite a bit
what is what has your life been like the
last like
eight months what what have you been
experiencing
uh it's been crazy um actually i work in
memory care
at a facility down in vancouver and
we haven't had like copied
like any positive um cases or anything
like that
until recently we had a couple
uh staff members
none of the residents or anything like
that um
but a couple of the staff members came
back positive
and i actually went to
modesto california um in
july i think for two weeks
uh for covid relief uh down there
and that was insane coveted relief like
what were you doing
california is pretty much a cesspool
yeah they they needed workers
they needed cna workers and um
it was a facility that's like a sister
facility with uh the company i work
work for and they needed people
and i volunteered along with one of my
friends who
also works with me and
everything was crazy because
they had a positive side which had like
40 i think 48 positive
uh covet residents
and then we had to wear
a ppe like gowns
face masks and face shields and
i was like this is this is wild like
they had
everything uh barricaded
with tarps and
everything it was it kind of reminded me
of
like the quarantine movies
that you watch and everything like that
i don't know
yeah like everybody's wearing hazmat
hazmats yeah i mean i can't imagine
having
tarps i i remember seeing towards the
beginning
it was just so crazy to see nurses
wearing
um like black trash bags and stuff and
there's just you know you said
tarps like that's just so weird it's so
different than our usual
what we would normally see so it has it
and that was back in july you said so
have you been
doing more more work with cobit patients
since you've gotten back
or was that that the one-time thing
it was just a one-time thing um yeah i
was only there for
two weeks and i actually had
when i got back i had to quarantine
for uh two weeks before i could go back
to work
and you know i got tested and everything
like that
um which
came back negative so i never had
cocaine
but do you question like the
[Music]
i feel like the test you see all this
stuff the test being insignificant and
stuff
or um not insignificant but
um they're just coming up it's like you
see a lot of stuff people say that
um the tests are negative sometimes a
positive sometimes and it's hard to
exactly quantify if people for sure have
it or have had it or not
yeah yeah because every single time that
i've been
tested it's like they do it differently
each time like uh
because it's a nasal swab and
there was one time i got tested and she
like barely even put it in my nose
and like you're supposed to actually
stick it up there pretty much in your
brain
uh and twist it
for like 10 seconds each nostril jesus
and yeah it's
it's it's not fun just intrusive at all
but yeah well yeah
because there's no way that you're
not gonna have tears coming out of your
eyes because it hurts
that bad yeah anything
right it just makes your eyes water yeah
it's
it's yeah it's weird
i don't know why they think that a nasal
swab
like is
you know right for the i don't know
everything's up in the air like i feel
like we're just trying
certain things and it's just i don't
know i think it's silly
i mean i guess there's yeah it is pretty
it's all
like everything about the whole thing
seems silly it's just like
of course i don't expect us to have like
you know as as a as a country or a world
or whatever to like perfectly handle
everything like oh this virus comes up
suddenly and we should be able to just
perfectly like okay we know exactly what
to do you know even if there is
playbooks or there's or there's
you know ways of handling it that have
been talked out before
it's not going to be pretty no matter
what it's like a very disrupting thing
for us so
i know that we're we're just trying to
figure it out i i so i had a test um
a couple months back and it was a blood
test
and i just had to get a finger prick and
then i sat there for
10 minutes and she came back in said i'm
negative
good to go and so i i don't know to me
it felt like the blood test was
i was like wow i trust that it seems
reliable it's a blood test
but i also don't really know i mean is
it more prone to show up in my snot or
in my blood
right well yeah because they say that
you know covid is more of like
in the lungs and everything like it's
um i mean that's where a lot of people
you know uh get really sick
because i think it can it's with the
whole pneumonia
and everything like that but it's a
different it attacks differently
than pneumonia but it's like
um why why the nasal swab
you know if it's not necessarily in your
sinuses or whatever i don't know
yeah it's a trial and error thing i
think
yeah it definitely is i think it'll be
interesting to look back you know and
say
10 years we look back at you know of
course covet is going to be
something that has changed our whole
society and the way we do a lot of
things and um
i heard this phrase phrase yesterday on
a podcast that was
someone was kind of half jokingly
calling it bc
like before kovid and now we're going to
call it something like some sort of
after coded
time frame which is so weird um but
i i don't know i it's just interesting
to look it's going to be interesting to
look back
and see what we what we kind of laugh at
ourselves for
or geez we could have done this better
or if we just simply did these things we
could have helped this many or
i don't know it's such a weird conundrum
and our the state of the media
does not freaking help our we're kind of
losing our minds when it comes to our
media and i think covid hitting right at
this time has just
projected that
um so you know what i would like to talk
about i agree
hey there's a little bit of a delay
but uh you know what i would like to
talk about shiloh is we met at
the 859.
what is your yes we did what is your
fondest memory of the 859 is there
anything that comes to mind immediately
of like
a good time you had there or
conversations you had there
or there was quite a few good ones
so let's let's describe two to the
listeners what the a59 was
like
sorry are you fine like
the 859 was
pretty much a party house
on was it was it seventh
yes avenue
yeah and the address was eight five nine
and pretty much every single day or
night
there was a party with
random people just all sorts of
different types of people
longview kelso kalama vancouver
gosh there was so many like
drunken heart to hearts there that
i don't even remember every single night
i remember
uh just out
on the porch on the little stoop
everyone's smoking or drinking
and just
got to that point of the night where
it's like oh dude
let's have a heart-to-heart but yeah i
don't know
or gosh
i spent so much time there that i can't
even like
there's so many different memories right
yeah it's like a stage in life of being
being update five nine for me
um i think because there was quite a few
for me um because it was just meeting
all these new people and i was a couple
years younger than everybody so i was
like
just felt so cool being invited to to
hang out with everyone
and um i remember there was the upstairs
like you're typical like i feel like you
would see
on a an instagram post where there's
just the upstairs room just full of
blankets and pillows and
you go up there and and smoke and just
hang out and relax and be comfortable
that was like such a such an inviting
place you can just really
be open and be yourself everybody i feel
like everybody was able to be themselves
at this house
because the people who lived there were
so accepting and
awesome and um for me let's see
there was this time where we had we had
a party
i'm not sure if you were there but we
there there was a party there that um
the edward sharp and the magnetic zeras
album had just come out
um the album that has home and um
40 days 40 nights it's just like one of
their their most popular albums
and um it had came out and i purchased
it and i pretty much was just like
taking people one by one into ryan
santos's room
like hey i want to show you a song and i
would invite them into the room to like
have them listen to this and just watch
them like hey this is good right you
love this right
it was just so so i don't know it was
just a legendary place man
it really was i remember
always there was always music all sorts
of different types of music
and like i think it was
ryan always had his laptop
playing like modest mouse and
uh just like
old old school like pop punk
type music and just feel good i don't
know
yeah the first time that i those are
good times for sure
yeah it was it's crazy like how long
it's been to the first time that i heard
i remember
specifically the first time i heard mgk
the rapper um
bo bo who was living there showed him to
me and i just remember being like oh wow
like
the amount of new music that was
introduced to to each other just by
everyone hanging out at that house
just a melting pot of new good music
yes and a lot of weed a lot of weed too
yeah i'm not sure if i oh yeah no yeah i
was smoking back then
uh i know we had and it's been a long
time
and i don't know if you participated in
this don't incriminate yourself it's
been a long time but i remember we had
molly parties there
actually um
yeah i was the babysitter
so you were very much appreciated at the
mali parties
yeah it was uh i was making sure that
everyone was drinking their orange fruit
yes taking care there's always the the
shaman figure who would take care of the
of the group going on their journey
thank you for that
yes you're welcome
i remember everyone
once they started rolling they would go
to the bathroom
they're like we gotta wash our hands
like what is going on right now
yep that that's that's how it's your
hands and
you guys
you guys would be in there for like a
half an hour
no way what is going on you're like ah
yeah oh it feels so good
it's funny to eat this sensory like you
guys are
whatever all of your your senses are so
heightened
uh man it's been so long since i've
participated in in the mdma world but
the your senses are so ultra heightened
um and you focus on like that's why like
you know people say touch you know you
like touch you see movies they talk
about ecstasy where it's just like this
whole like
um romanticized like
touching side of things but there really
is kind of that aspect you just
appreciate you're like
wow i never realized how much i
appreciate the contrast of
cold to hot water like these things that
seem profound to you
while you're while you're rolling away
yeah or like touching the wall
like the text texture and everything was
like
i'm just like what am i watching right
now i'm just drinking beer
yeah yeah it's it's fun
it's cool to see you know it was like
that so long ago
um but now they're doing so much
good research and so many good trials
and and
clinically helping people with ptsd
helping people with severe depression
anxiety
like all the all the research that's
going into mdma
assisted therapy is just so cool to
think about because
you know there's there's a difference
between experiencing something like that
you know when you're with your friends
which which is great or when you're
you know at a festival or a show or
something
which i have done a couple times before
as well
and then having the
like the the act of taking something
like that
and then having headphones a comfortable
spot
um you're in the right setting setting
um i think
as far as these the clinical trials are
going it's like two people who are
assisting you like two therapists are
with you and they're kind of just there
for you and they're guiding you through
some things and
they have the right playlists ready for
you and you can kind of
go through maybe your old traumas or
your old um
you know stories or things that are kind
of holding you back
and it seems like they dig those up man
i'm just i'm
super excited to see the future of what
they do with that you know
really interesting i didn't know that
oh yeah yeah they're doing a ton of work
with all that with um
i mean psychedelic assisted therapy too
like um
psilocybin lsd that sort of thing i
don't know where all of it's at
there's always a lot of red tape and
there's a lot like different
places different states have different
things that they're trying out but
yeah maps m-a m-a-p-s they're doing a
ton of
a ton of work for psychedelic assisted
therapy mdma assisted therapy
i'm really excited for the future of it
like if we can
you know not have you know it seems like
we have our answer to a lot of
anything when it comes to the brain is
just like anxiety meds or depression
meds
and you know i feel like doctors don't
entirely know what to do you know
they're just doing their best they're
they're taking the information they they
learned from schooling
and applying it to people who are coming
in saying like hey
i'm feeling monumental despair at all
times in the day can you help
so having some other some other thing
that can help people
is going to be very exciting
that's really cool and it's exciting
yeah um how do you think shiloh
this might be a tough question how do
you think
you have changed as a person since like
i mean it's
what 10 years eight five nine days as we
we grow um i mean we're always growing
we're always learning more
leaning more into our adult selves is
there anything that you can think of
that comes to mind immediately of um
like how have you changed how have you
grown
since those days before
um see i
moved i moved out of state
um i'm into arizona
and i lived in san diego um
i think oh man that is a tough question
i think i know more of who i
am as a person now than
what i did back then because
i didn't really know myself at all
like yeah you know i partied and stuff
like that
and you know moving away from
everything that i've ever known to
knowing no one um
kind of made me
see life in a different perspective than
just
uh partying and everything like
i would go out hiking and i don't know
it's
kind of hard to explain i guess
yeah i just kind of found myself more
no i i i get that i mean i think
yeah i think you know especially i think
growing up
did you grow up in in town around here
your whole life were you were you born
in in this area in college county
yep yeah nice yeah
man i love castle rock um but it's
it's interesting because i think a lot
of people who don't
move around a lot you don't realize kind
of like what's out there or you don't
realize like
as much of who you are is so influenced
by
everyone you're around in your
upbringing and the town you live in and
the things you're doing
um which isn't isn't always a bad thing
but i think when you get out there
get out into the world and you put
yourself in different situations where
you're kind of just at a blank slate
with life with who you are
you're you you can like meet new people
and you know be completely who you want
to be without their
um you know maybe like
placement of who they think you are or
who they remember you as like
if you if you like pooped your pants
when you were 15 years old in high
school
and you still see you still see people
who were in the class with you
10 years later they're still pregnant a
joke can call you poopy pants or
something so
it's nice to move away and um
you know experience that that clean
slate for me
when i started um traveling traveling
for work
and traveling for things in high school
like i went up to even just bellevue
when i started leaving town i was like
wow look this is people live differently
here there's you know i would see uh
see a ferrari in real life and be like
wow wow those are really cool looking
you know it's crazy how much just
getting out of your town and really
trying to absorb the new places that
you're going to
can really help you change but it's a
change
more towards who you really are it seems
like
yeah exactly and
like it was the hardest experience that
i've
ever had to do but it was the best
experience
as well because you know moving away
from everything that people
friends family and
going to a new place where you know no
one like
that was really hard like i kind of
um i kind of isolated myself for a while
like once i moved because it's like
oh my gosh like what am i gonna do
like i have no friends like but i
started to get more independent
to once i left because i would go
do things by myself since i didn't know
anybody
you know instead of if i lived here i'd
call up a friend be like hey you want to
go to the mall
with me or you want to go get some lunch
like i would just do things by myself
a lot but
yeah i think um that
the the act of like doing because it's
like you know you're kind of faced with
okay i have all these friends back at
home but if i
when i move away you gotta almost put
yourself out there so to say you know we
heard that phrase before but you kind of
almost like hey if i want to make
friends i need to like
find a way to connect with people and
see you know what
what they like or you know maybe i gotta
find someone who likes the same music as
me or i gotta find someone who
um is into the things that i am and then
you you gotta try
forming that friendship it's hard man
because it's it's comfy to just
chill by yourself but that growth is on
the other side of kind of putting
yourself out there a lot of the times
exactly exactly and
that's what i started doing too i would
you know i found like a venue
um that would have you know
shows hardcore shows
and everything so i started going to
shows by myself
and then meeting new people which was
fun
and it was cool going to a different
venue
than i'm used to and it ended up being
the coolest venue i've
ever went to what what venue was that
uh the nile in
phoenix actually mesa
hmm
really really cool because they had like
they had an upstairs which was huge
and then they had a basement for
uh shows as well so would they
would they play would they play like
different music upstairs than they would
downstairs
not necessarily um
i think more so
downstairs they had a lot of like
hardcore bands
uh but
they also did shows upstairs
with hardcore bands as well i think it
depended on
uh the how many bands
we're playing on the bill
so yeah imagine the imagine like
when shows open back up like whatever
that looks like after you know our cove
would
run here um like
i know that i i'll just be happy to go
to like
if there's some dude who just learned
how to play guitar and is just
off-key yelling into the mic at an open
mic night i will be so content i don't
even care i just want to see
live music i don't care if it's a dj
train wrecking who's terrible at djing
i don't care if it's like the worst ac
dc cover band ever
i just want to see some live music
what's the
what's the last live show that you
remember going to before covet
um
[__] it's been a while since i've
been the last one i think was russ
and that was a couple years ago hmm
was that was that in portland i think i
went to i went to one of the more recent
rest shows but yeah it's been a long
time now
yeah yeah was that uh
i think it was at the moto center
yeah i um yeah that was fun i'm i'm
looking forward to
when we're able to go to concerts again
who knows
when that's going to be um yeah it's
just it's so weird like
because i work in live events and i you
know djing audio engineering
even just you know do a lot of stagehand
type stuff
so i miss it in that aspect because my
whole life has just like flipped and i'm
not doing the things that i love doing
for work but it's also
right like i'm just excited for
being able to go to shows because it's
going to be a while before there's
massive big shows where there's a ton of
people
i know
um sorry no you're good
shiloh i did want to talk about um you
know something we're all going through
you know we
were losing we lost live events um
we lost like our whole way of being
before
we're all we're all adjusting but i
think that something that we had message
back and forth that would be
beneficial to talk about is loss and how
we navigate through loss the loss that
we've experienced
i think everybody of course in the year
2020 has experienced some sort of loss
some sort of losing
losing something that they had before
losing the way that we lived
before it's something
that we could all use a little
perspective on i think so just
i think hearing anybody's journey of
loss and how loss has changed them and
how they're
coping with it and maybe how they're not
coping with it so well even just to
to not feel so so alone you know because
it's like i've had my own troubles you
know i've i've experienced a lot of loss
just like a lot of other people this
year
and um you know i'm doing my best but i
think just hearing
other people also going through it snaps
us out of this
um like oh i'm not doing well because
there's
i've this much has changed since covetor
i
i'm you know we get kind of down on
ourselves for not
being exactly where we want to be but i
think there's so much loss in this time
in so many ways
that we're all just kind of stumbling
through it um
what's what's been your experience with
loss since the pandemic started
um well
in april i lost
two really good friends of mine
um you probably know one of them
one second clayton
that was really tough because it was
like
you know i
had lost touch you know with him like
yeah we would talk like over like
snapchat and everything i know he
lived up in seattle but
i think the hardest part about
that one is just
losing touch and
that took a while to kind of
get over obviously it's not
it's always going to be there but just
kind of
moving on from being depressed
about it because um
yeah it was just really really hard and
kind of unexpected
and then the two weeks before that
i had a friend drown in
silver lake and that was
also unexpected um
it was a freak kayaking
accident and
didn't have a life jacket on
and everything and i guess he didn't
know how to swim
and you know that was really really hard
because i had just
talked to this person like two days
before that
and we were making plans to
um
make dinner and everything like that and
then two days later
he's gone
and then just recently i don't know if
you knew her
uh sarah brooks
yeah yeah
she just passed away a couple weeks ago
i don't know if you knew that i did it
uh wow um yeah sorry
no that's that's that's how it goes
that's uh i i didn't know her super well
i
i think that she if i remember right she
worked at the mall when i was working at
the mall
she she did hair right
yeah okay yeah yeah wow
well so so i mean i i think that
what what you're going through um a good
amount of people are
are going through as well so i mean
thanks for sharing it just it's hard to
even like talk about you know
is like who knows what is what's the
proper etiquette for talking about
such great lots of of friends you know
there's there's not so thanks for
sharing that but
it's it makes you
kind of it's just like we're you know
when we're losing our other ways of
being you know we even as
casually as concerts like we don't get
to go to concerts anymore well
it makes you kind of kind of
want to value you know your next concert
you want to value it that much more
and i think it um sometimes loss when it
comes to
loved ones is is this you know there's
so much sadness around there's so much
sorrow there's so much confusion but
there's also sometimes with a little bit
of time you can
have value from
okay i want to make sure that i'm trying
to be present in the future with my
friends i want to really value my
friends i want to
you know because we could we can this
can all change in such a quick instant
we can um you know because we we do lose
touch
and it's just kind of the way that
things go we we separate
we move in different ways in our life we
can't
possibly just constantly be texting or
talking to every single person we
know um so just i think for me when it
comes to loss
i like to just at the end of the day
you've got to just value the time that
you did have with them
right it's it's so overly obvious but
when you can just work on your state of
mind
and really being with someone like wow i
really value you like you know if
if you left this earth soon i would
sincerely miss you and so that makes
this time
that much more special that i want to
spend with you and
shiloh i think that a lot of people are
going to
um have that kind of that kind of let
lesson to be learned because there's
there's a lot of
there's a lot of loss going on you know
people
people right now are mental health is
just not
the a lot of people are suffering right
now
you know um we're we're locked in like
our whole way of life all the fun stuff
that we used to do
um we're all we're all adjusting to it
so
i think that i think that
it's hard to see it right now um and
it's hard to just try to like throw
optimism at everything you know but
there is
value to um
just trying to trying to see like what
has this taught me and how do i feel
about this
and what does that mean for the future
for me like what does that mean for
how i want to value my relationships
going forward you know how are you
how are you how are you doing with
everything like how
are you are you um
are you finding like good good ways to
cope are you trying to like
treat yourself well or like how are you
doing with all of it
i mean okay um
honestly i try to keep busy
you know i work a lot and so
just working
and um
yeah just trying to find things to keep
myself
busy so it's not
so i'm not a
like thinking about it 24 7.
you know what i mean like i will come
home
uh from work i get off at 10 but
i work in vancouver and live in
casserock so
i get home around 11 and
i just kind of that's
when i kind of uh unwind and i start
to kind of process everything because
even though keeping busy is good
but it's also good to kind of process of
what you're going through
and you know i watch a lot of tick tock
videos too
so just kind of get a laugh out of me
and you know i'm glad i have my
my puppy you know she keeps me
you know it's that unconditional love
from a dog
oh yes i know that well
yeah and you know she
it's so crazy how um
dogs can sense that you're upset
and everything and you know she
she likes to be close by and that just
makes me
makes it that
i don't know just that warm comfort
feeling
totally yeah i agree i think dogs have
that
it's just that little their little paw
on your lap just says
everything's gonna be okay
they have that that knack for being able
to like you said
sense when when they're human when their
companion friend
is is down and they just know
immediately they're like oh
my human is bummed i need to give them
some snuggles you know
it's it's a magical thing dogs
yeah like um
i don't know like a couple weeks ago
when i you know
was going through crying every day and
everything and
you know georgia would uh come over to
me and lick
like the tears off my face and i'm just
like i don't want you looking my face
but it's just the cutest
sweetest little thing and you know
it's sweet yeah they have that ability
to
yeah they have that ability to sense
exactly what you need or pull you out of
kind of like if you're if you've just
been looping the same thoughts kind of
sometimes just
especially when you come home from work
when they're just unconditionally
excited to see you you're just like you
don't even think about what you were
thinking about on the car ride home
you're just
so happy to to put your face in with
their face and snuggle
um i i've experienced that with my dog
blue
um you know because he's kind of going
through
like when shaylee and i separated it's
you know it's a lot of like staying at
this house and staying at this house and
moving and um you know he's along for
the ride he's got to like
stay in a place that he's not used to
and he's got to have his
schedule switched around so he was
really stressed
but he could also you know kind of pick
up off of our vibes
and pick off off our stress too and so
it's it's just so interesting to see how
much they they mimic
our anxiousness and then they also
sense it to help fix it you know they
they just
dogs cats a lot of the times um
they just know what to do they just know
what their human needs and they give
them some snuggles
right yeah because you know they know
your routine
just as much as you know their routine
and it's like
if that routine is um
you know uh
tampered with you know it's like they
know
it's like my human is off this is not
right
but i'm gonna go give them some snuggles
yeah there's a um a philosopher
um rupert sheldrake he actually has
all these studies i haven't i haven't
studied into it a ton but i've kind of
heard him talk about it
he has these studies where they
basically tested a bunch of different
animals
and um and and basically the
the thing was to prove that animals have
some sort of
sense when their human has come home so
basically they tested a bunch of
different um homes
and they tested um like so say you you
come home from work and your dog's like
a few minutes before 10 minutes before
five minutes before
he's already excited before you're like
in the driveway before he can hear your
car
and they even had the had the people
come home at different times in the day
they had the people drive different cars
so the dog can't like hear the same
car and there was just a ton of positive
um
basically proving that the the dogs and
the cats would
sense when their owners are about to be
home and it's just so interesting to
think you know like what there's these
connections between animals that we
don't explore that much but we all kind
of within our own
animals we're like we get it we there's
this wink that's going on between us and
our dogs
yeah yeah
animals are fascinating they really are
because you know we don't know what's
going on in there
my dog what do you mean
sorry sure okay okay
all that i'll give them a call soon all
right
wow interesting we're talking about dogs
and uh where i was saying we're
experiencing
the kennel cough stuff um and we weren't
sure if my dog blew had gotten it but
they're trying to get a hold of me
because my dog is um
not doing well with kennel cough i guess
so i guess he did get it
so i'll uh i'll give him a call after
after our podcast here poor guy
oh man poor little bud
well um there's a couple things that i
wanted to talk about i
i do want to i feel like you always have
good taste in music i want to shift over
to music
um what have you been listening to
a ton of christmas music i bet you've
been listening a ton of christmas music
right
uh no no
only at work but that's because
it's work um
what have i been listening to um
honestly in the last like couple days
i've been listening to marilyn manson
so um
but like new music i've been listening
to the
new joyner uh lucas album
evolution i think i think that's what
it's called
i haven't heard it yet oh
it's straight fire ooh i need to get in
on it then i love joining lucas
it's so good i think it dropped like a
couple weeks ago
so um and also joji i've been listening
to a lot of joji
joji has that it's very original right
like joji
has that like because there's this new
i don't know what what genre would you
even say joji is it's kind of like this
like
punk bedroom hip-hop uh
like i don't know it's a very very
original sound like it represents kind
of the internet culture i feel like
yeah i don't even know what genre i
would
even put him in probably his own
like you said he's very original like i
don't know
he's got that swag about him that i just
love
yeah i uh um i remember
i feel like so i just had the the
spotify i don't know if you use spotify
but they have like a year year
in review thing and they see the songs
that you listen to and
how many genres you listen to and it's
just so weird to think about
like when i first started djing there
was
there's all these subgenres but there's
just kind of like your main genres
and then just over time everybody's
creating their own sound they're kind of
like going off in this direction
they're mixing this with this and
now there's like i think it said that i
have
i listened to 183 new genres in the year
2020 and it's like what how does that
even there's that many new genres to
listen to let alone i listen to them you
know it's crazy
right yeah i think
mine was about right around that uh
number two and i listened to like
close to 2 000 new artists
i'm like didn't even know but
that's cool crazy yeah i mean
before you used to have to like if you
wanted to be an artist to come up in the
game you had to you know get a record
label
you had to like find the right people
you have to have everything
professionally done but now it's like
the internet just changes it if you've
got something to say you know
the zeitgeist of people online will find
your stuff and share
it and you know there's all these
different new ways to
get your music out there like whether
it's youtube or tick-tock even tick-tock
is huge for new artists right now
yeah it's it's insane like
i remember like myspace i remember a lot
of people
use myspace for you know
getting their music out and it's just
like a
sound cloud but you know it's my space
and everything i miss my space me too
i miss being able to when you go to
someone's profile you immediately have a
song playing
that was the coolest thing it's just
like welcome to my house
here's what i'm all about you just get a
just have music playing right when they
get to meet you and
man that was i feel like myspace was was
the coolest
i miss my space yeah especially you know
you gotta
create you got to be a creator of like
your profile
in everything and yeah putting music on
there
having a playlist i don't know haven't
having
glitter graphics learning how to use
html somehow
exactly
we definitely figured it out i i i feel
like it uh
when i would discover like emo pop punk
bands
on there i would just be like obsessed
with them that was like the best way to
find new
um kind of pop punk bands was through
myspace it's interesting to think of
what what that era was for us when it
comes to myspace and like those bands
that we listen to
um now you know the the tick tock the
people
growing up with tick tock right now are
discovering what's going to be their
like pop punk of their generation you
know right
i remember with myspace like
i before like a day to remember
like was big like i discovered them
and i was like oh this band's so cool
and then
saw him at warped tour and
that's another thing you know go on a
warp tour
i i discovered a lot of like
new bands and stuff like that
like new music yeah
warped tour was i used to go to a ton of
warped tours like
just being able to walk around like
you'd have your list of like bands that
you want to see
so warped tour was definitely one you
could wander around and just follow your
ears
or like go down a lot of times i feel
like we would choose the bands based off
of their merch sometimes
like if they had cool merch and we
hadn't ever heard about them we'd be
like cool let's go what time were they
playing let's go check them out they got
cool merch
was sick man it was
r.i.p oh man yeah even before covet i
think that they were done i think that
they
hung up the reigns on warped tour yeah i
think they did
uh 20 years or something like that 25
years
it might have been 30 actually because i
think they started in the
early 90s yeah that's that's another
thing that
i feel like can change you is just going
to going to concerts and going to like
festivals
and stuff and just because a lot of the
warped tour vibe
for me anyway and i don't know if it was
like this for you a lot of it was like
me and you know a couple of my close
friends are into these things but
otherwise i felt like a big old sore
thumb i felt like a black sheep kind of
of
like oh i'm the one dressing in the
black and i'm wearing the eyeliner and
i'm wearing the
tight black pants you know and then you
get almost made fun of in a town like
ours growing up anyway
and then you go to warped tour and
people are giving you compliments on
everything you're wearing
and um you're you're meeting new people
based off of like the artist you're both
watching and you're
bumping into friends that like have the
same interest
as you it's it's pretty cool
yeah that's that's exactly how i felt
too because like
um i think it was starting in sixth
grade
sixth or seventh grade you know wearing
all black
wearing the bracelets and uh you know
drawing on my shoes and like the
converse
and it was always like that
up until i think junior year
and going to warp to her was like i'm
home
you know you felt completely accepted
yeah instead of that's how it was
um yeah i think a lot of kids are
man i just think of like the there was a
few prim like
a few huge years of my life where i was
like
growing into myself you know where
you're when you get to
when you like the things that you like
but you're around a bunch of people who
don't really like those things it's hard
sometimes you question like what you
like especially when you're a young kid
growing up you're like i don't know like
should i should i be doing the things
that other people are doing am i
spending time on the wrong things and
then you'd go to a place like warped
tour
or for me after that even like when i
started going to raves
um that's kind of how it was for me just
this huge acceptance
of the things that i wanted to do and
what i was wearing and who i was being
and you know singing out loud and
dancing and these sort of things
um it's interesting to think that the
age right now
not not only just during covid but even
just the last few years in the years
projecting
they kind of get that acceptance from
the internet you know whereas we used to
go
find these places where there's just you
know a
a big old field full of misfits
at warped tour where you get to go fit
in now
they're they're fighting these
communities online now it's it's very
it's interesting to think of how how
different the younger generations are
going to think from those sort of things
right like technology has
you know we're going into like
the future like futuristic type thing
because you know zoom calls and
doing online schooling and um
just it's completely different
than when we grew up and everything like
that you know
it because yeah we did have the internet
and
everything but it was brand new pretty
much
you know dial up
and everything and now we everyone has
um an ipad
a cell phone and
just technology has just skyrocketed
in the last like 10 years yeah
it's it's gonna change a lot of a lot of
everything and
technology has definitely been
exponentially like kicked in the ass
and and really pushed forward with kobit
because we're just kind of forced in our
houses online so
it'll be very interesting i i really
like exploring and kind of
like contemplating and thinking about
what the future is going to be with all
this
this new technology and how the you know
the young kids right now how are they
going to be
as adults you know and how are they
going to change the world and how are
they going to see the world differently
and and how is that going to work out
with everybody who you know because
there's still going to be people
who are alive living in the same society
as them who
didn't really have any internet use and
the most internet use they get nowadays
is
you know zoom calls in these sort of
things so it's going to be a cool
cool mixture of people because we grew
up we grew up just like illegally
downloading songs off limewire
and now it's like you really got to
search for your songs back then and a
lot of times you
you know you think you're downloading
the link in park album but it's
some other like terrible rapper who just
used the linkin park name and you had to
download it but uh now they get to just
go to spotify and just they control
what they listen to at all times they
don't want to listen to the rest of the
song
next as soon as an artist releases a
song they get to go see it it's like a
notification to their phone so even just
music changing is
it's going to be super cool man i'm i'm
very interested to see how the
the future of technology music and
you know young people just changes the
way we do everything
well yeah in the last like what three or
four years like
you know you were talking about um you
know music
back then like needed a
a record deal and everything like that
but now
everyone's doing it uh
like themselves
and everything which is so cool to me
even like big bands
too they have their own
record label and they're doing their
music
themselves instead of having to go
through
hoops and everything like that with the
record manager
and blah blah blah but i think it's
really cool
yeah yeah it's it's cool to see the you
know we could really
give the artists back their control in a
sense they don't have to do it this way
to make sure it gets marketed and
you know there is those aspects of
social media and all the things you have
to do differently
when you're putting your band out there
but there's
i mean the creative control the fact
that like i can be in in my spot here
and you know make beats or like little
young kids can be
making beats um and then they could they
don't have to go to a studio to get it
to sound pretty decent there's so many
plug-ins and tools and different like
pieces of technology that
make what we're making sound pretty good
so you can
go more streamlined from you know an
artist having an idea in their head
onto you know the the sound paper like
on to actually recording a track
and you get to communicate that thought
in your head just so much faster you
don't have to wait a few years for it to
go to the
you know get it mixed and mastered and
then your label has to do
to distribute it and all these things so
it's it's really cool we're getting more
more direct with music
and i'm really interested to see what
these young people do with it yeah
yeah um i so we're
i'm admittedly just thinking about my
dog shiloh so we're gonna have to cut
this a little bit short
but i do want to if there's any message
you think that the world needs to hear
definitely hit me with it but i've been
trying to
figure out a an ending question
sometimes i think about i ask people
about
legacy like what's the legacy you want
to leave or
i've been enjoying asking what do you
think the world could use
more of right now um does anything pop
in your mind for that like what what
does the world
need a little bit more of right now in
this time
hmm
i think the world needs a little more
of
i don't know that's a tough one because
there's a lot
i don't know you know we're in a
this year 2020 has been a roller coaster
to say the least i think
a lot of people need more
i don't know i can't even think of
anything
right now
i think the world needs more dogs how
about that
hey i can i can roll with that i think
the world does need more dogs
and look at this dog
she is very cute i think the world could
use more dogs i i
i'm actually with you let's just go with
the world needs more dogs
okay i mean
we were talking about the you know the
joy that you get from
having a dog that unconditional love
like they're just there for you because
a lot of us you know the comfort that
that animals can bring
us because a lot of us are kind of going
through
just so many changes loss difference
adjustments a lot of hard work to try to
like
just adjust all of our lives to what's
actually going on now
and dogs have a knack for bringing you
kind of
back down to earth like what's really
here like okay
this dog with this wagon tail is joyful
right now you know there's a lot going
on
but oh yeah everything's gonna be okay
and my dog is a stark reminder of that
exactly sounds good to me
okay the world needs more dogs
yeah she's very cute man she how old is
she
uh she is
ten and a half months oh yeah not i
think
just a little bit older than blue i feel
like blue is right around
right around that age i don't know his
exact birthday but
yeah super cool um actually no she's 11
months
my bad oh she's got offended
she'll be older she'll be one in january
so okay okay okay yeah well dogs are a
blessing i encourage anybody to
um adopt or buy a dog or give them a
loving home
and you can just see what it what it
changes in it for me
it having a dog made me realize how
i thought i was more patient than i
actually am and
made me realize how like when you're
when you're potty training a dog you
know i'd be like i'll just get ticked
off all the time or i'd get annoyed
because he would just
walk us around for 15 minutes outside
without going potty and all these things
but
it's good to learn patience especially
in this time
exactly and they're good
good with that yeah
dogs are good teachers and they're good
um
you know comfort blades so get a dog my
friends get a dog
um shiloh i am going to wrap it up here
i very much appreciate you taking the
time out of your day to chat with me
and share kind of what's going on in
your life right now um
thank you for being vulnerable and just
like talking about stuff you know i
think that that's so much helpful to
people just
hearing people who who are also going
through stuff
right now you know we're all just human
trying to figure this thing out
and right now is a it's a particularly
weird difficult
time so just being able to to share our
our fellow humanity with our fellow
humans
is helpful so i thank you for being on
the podcast shiloh
yeah thanks for having me it was a
pleasure
yeah you betcha we will uh we'll catch
up soon i'll send you a text a little
bit later today okay
listeners have a good rest of your day
if you haven't drank any water you got
to be drinking some water and if you
don't have a dog
you got to get a dog man you should buy
a dog right now this is just
this is my recommendation go buy a dog
and make sure you can take care of the
guy but
we all need more dogs
have a good rest of your day
[Music]
knowledge is power
you